



# Leonardo da Cunha Machado

Nationality: Brazilian Date of birth: 18/04/1981 Gender: Male

**Capacita** Phone number: (+351) 961543311

Email address: <a href="mailto:leonardomachado10@yahoo.com.br">leonardomachado10@yahoo.com.br</a>

• Home: Rua Jose Maria Ottoni 49, 4715-309 Braga (Portugal)

## **ABOUT ME**

 ${\sf GWO~BST/SS/BTT/EFA/ART~H+N/SART~H/SLINGER~SIGNALLER/BLADE~REPAIR}$ 

Winda: LD044674BR

Rope Access IRATA L1
OEUK/OGUK Offshore Medical
Chester Step
ACTSAFE Training
HAILO Ladder Service Lift

Industrial Maintenance Technician Inspector NDT (PT MT UT)

**GE Site Induction** 

Vestas SIT - ESO - Fire Prevention Awareness - Installation Add on - Tower Installation

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Wind Turbine Technician

**Endiprev SA** [ 06/2023 - 05/2024 ]

City: Saint Nazaire | Country: France

- Rope Access Activities, Preventive and Corrective Maintenance Services on Haliade-150 at GE Wind Farm in France, PBG Offshore.
- Assembly and Commissioning Service on Haliade-X Nacelles at the GE Factory in Saint Nazaire.
- Preventive and Corrective Maintenance at GE 1x, 2x, 3x, Cypress Wind Farms in Portugal.

## **Blade Repair Technician**

**Onrope** [ 09/2022 - 06/2023 ]

Country: Portugal

LPS Internal,

Damage 1Cat and 3Cat (Hard back, Bonding, Inner Layer, vacuum, Paint),

Sensors Remove External

Inspection External and Internal

Flash Over

Rope Access and Plataform

#### **Industrial Mechanical Techinician**

**Continental Pneus** [ 07/2021 – 08/2022 ]

City: Lousado | Country: Portugal

I worked as an Industrial Mechanical Technician, carrying out Preventive and Corrective Maintenance on various Machines and equipment, carrying out Mechanical, Electrical, Hydraulic and Pneumatic Repairs, installation and assembly of modules, engines, parts and accessories.

## **Equipment Inspection an Maintenance Technician**

Mariner Serviços Subaquaticos [ 04/2016 – 01/2020 ]

City: Macae | Country: Brazil

Onshore and Offshore Maintenance and Inspection Services for Drilling Equipment and Anchoring and Nautical Accessories for Tug Vessels and Petroleum Platforms PETROBRAS, acting as Preventive and Corrective Maintenance Technician and Non-Destructive Testing Inspector of Penetrating Liquid, Magnetic Particles, issuing reports and final reports, working with ASME STANDARDS and PETROBRAS STANDARDS.

## **Inspector NDT and IRATA L1**

**Derrick Services UK** [ 12/2013 – 10/2015 ]

City: Macae | Country: Brazil

Offshore services Rope access and NDT inspection on oil platforms, performing Ultrasound Inspection, magnetic particles, dye penetrant check and thickness measurement on welds and platform structures. Issuing reports and final reports, working with the ASME STANDARD and the PETROBRAS STANDARDS.

## **Inspection Technician**

**Axess** [ 05/2011 - 11/2013 ]

City: Rio de Janeiro | Country: Brazil

Offshore services NDT Inspection and LGI, performing inspection of Magnetic Particles, Penetrating Liquid and Thickness measurement in welds, piping and naval equipment.

## **Inspection Technician and Load Test Operator**

**Atrac Brasil** [ 02/2008 – 04/2011 ]

City: Rio de Janeiro | Country: Brazil

Offshore Services of NDT inspection on welds and equipments, Load Test on Cranes and Lift Gears.

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

## **Industrial Maintenance Technician**

**Escola Tecnica Senai** [ 01/2008 – 04/2010 ]

City: Rio de Janeiro | Country: Brazil

### Inspector NDT Test ( UT PT MP ME )

**Senai, Abendi** [ 02/2005 – 02/2007 ]

City: Rio de Janeiro | Country: Brazil

### **IRATA L1**

**Outside Academy** [ 05/2023 ]

City: Porto | Country: Portugal

#### **OEUK/OGUK + CHESTER STEP - Offshore Medical**

**Ceniude** [ 04/2024 ]

City: Lisboa | Country: Portugal

### **GWO BST**

**GWO** [ 03/2023 ]

City: Sevilha | Country: Spain

### **GWO Sea Survival**

**Onrope** [ 01/2024 ]

City: Porto | Country: Portugal

## **GWO Blade Repair**

**GWO** [ 03/2023 ]

City: Sevilha | Country: Spain

#### **GWO BTT**

**Onrope** [ 11/2023 ]

City: Porto | Country: Portugal

## **GWO Slinger Signaller**

**Onrope** [ 03/2024 ]

City: Porto | Country: Portugal

#### **GWO EFA**

**Onrope** [ 01/2024 ]

City: Porto | Country: Portugal

#### **GWO ART H+N**

**Onrope** [ 11/2023 ]

City: Porto | Country: Portugal

### **GWO SART H**

**Onrope** [ 03/2024 ]

City: Porto | Country: Portugal

### **ACTSAFE Training**

**Onrope** [ 03/2024 ]

City: Porto | Country: Portugal

### **HAILO LADDER Service Lift**

**Hailo** [ 01/2024 ]

City: Porto | Country: Portugal

## Safety When Working on or Near Electrical Installations L-AUS

**EKU** [ 11/2023 ]

City: E-Learning | Country: Portugal | Website: www.eku.dk

#### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): Portuguese

## Other language(s):

## **English**

LISTENING A2 READING B1 WRITING A2

#### **SPOKEN PRODUCTION A2 SPOKEN INTERACTION A2**

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

### **DRIVING LICENCE**

Driving Licence: A1
Driving Licence: B1
Driving Licence: B

### **EXTRA**

## **Summary**

I have 11 years of experience Offshore and Onshore Experience in Mechanical Technician

A lot of experience in NDT Inspection,

Experience in using sanders and angle grinders,

I am looking for an opportunity in the Wind Industry, or NDT Test,

I'm taking an English course at the moment to improve myself.

Thank you very much.